const quizDataFromFile = [
  {
    "question": "ab",
    "correct": "from",
    "choices": [
      "to be closed",
      "moment",
      "from",
      "homepage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "aber",
    "correct": "but",
    "choices": [
      "soft",
      "move",
      "but",
      "basketball"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Angebot",
    "correct": "offer",
    "choices": [
      "bus",
      "offer",
      "program / show / broadcast",
      "permission"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "anders",
    "correct": "different",
    "choices": [
      "water",
      "baby",
      "different",
      "paper"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Achtung",
    "correct": "Attention!",
    "choices": [
      "pullover",
      "Attention!",
      "E-Book",
      "answer / decision / information"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Adresse",
    "correct": "address",
    "choices": [
      "neck",
      "cash register",
      "address",
      "room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Anfang",
    "correct": "Beginning",
    "choices": [
      "Beginning",
      "boots",
      "Youth (female)",
      "map / city map"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Angst",
    "correct": "anxiety / fear",
    "choices": [
      "anxiety / fear",
      "soccer",
      "to be away",
      "address"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ahnung",
    "correct": "idea",
    "choices": [
      "poor",
      "text",
      "potato",
      "idea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "aktiv",
    "correct": "active",
    "choices": [
      "outside",
      "to do",
      "to be allowed",
      "active"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "aktuell",
    "correct": "current",
    "choices": [
      "TV",
      "dead",
      "famous",
      "current"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "alles",
    "correct": "everything",
    "choices": [
      "printer",
      "greeting",
      "everything",
      "forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "alle",
    "correct": "all",
    "choices": [
      "wife",
      "French fries",
      "delay",
      "all"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ankunft",
    "correct": "Arrival",
    "choices": [
      "both",
      "household",
      "suitcase",
      "Arrival"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Anmeldung",
    "correct": "registration",
    "choices": [
      "earlier",
      "now",
      "registration",
      "new"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Anrufbeantworter",
    "correct": "Answering machine",
    "choices": [
      "fork",
      "cake",
      "Fashion",
      "Answering machine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Anruf",
    "correct": "Call",
    "choices": [
      "about that",
      "Call",
      "key",
      "lazy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "allein",
    "correct": "alone",
    "choices": [
      "message",
      "enough",
      "alone",
      "recipe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "als",
    "correct": "as",
    "choices": [
      "ear",
      "as",
      "tired",
      "nearly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "also",
    "correct": "so",
    "choices": [
      "toilet",
      "so",
      "man",
      "accommodation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Anschluss",
    "correct": "connection",
    "choices": [
      "Bank (Money Institution)",
      "female student / pupil",
      "(to go) there",
      "connection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Antwort",
    "correct": "answer",
    "choices": [
      "heavy",
      "thin",
      "answer",
      "club"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "alt",
    "correct": "old",
    "choices": [
      "old",
      "equal",
      "floor",
      "Bean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Alter",
    "correct": "age",
    "choices": [
      "more",
      "glasses",
      "word",
      "age"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ampel",
    "correct": "traffic light",
    "choices": [
      "blond",
      "traffic light",
      "entry",
      "Colour"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "an",
    "correct": "at",
    "choices": [
      "suggestion",
      "at",
      "sometimes",
      "late"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Anzeige",
    "correct": "display",
    "choices": [
      "display",
      "empty",
      "invitation",
      "lazy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Anzug",
    "correct": "suit",
    "choices": [
      "number",
      "T-Shirt",
      "portion",
      "suit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Apfel",
    "correct": "Apple",
    "choices": [
      "Apple",
      "again",
      "how much",
      "festival"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Apotheke",
    "correct": "pharmacy",
    "choices": [
      "therefore / that's why",
      "pharmacy",
      "hobby",
      "nearly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Apparat",
    "correct": "device / machine",
    "choices": [
      "device / machine",
      "on-line",
      "blond",
      "Bean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "aus",
    "correct": "out",
    "choices": [
      "out",
      "accurate / exact",
      "delay",
      "to be up"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Arbeit",
    "correct": "job",
    "choices": [
      "job",
      "exciting",
      "light",
      "from where"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ausbildung",
    "correct": "education",
    "choices": [
      "education",
      "to whom / to who",
      "knife",
      "in"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ausflug",
    "correct": "Excursion",
    "choices": [
      "exciting",
      "Excursion",
      "wish",
      "pregnant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "arbeitslos",
    "correct": "unemployed",
    "choices": [
      "unemployed",
      "bath",
      "body",
      "female neighbor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "arm",
    "correct": "poor",
    "choices": [
      "sick",
      "track",
      "poor",
      "tip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Arm",
    "correct": "arm",
    "choices": [
      "far",
      "company",
      "house",
      "arm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ausgang",
    "correct": "exit",
    "choices": [
      "congratulation",
      "exit",
      "vacation",
      "thing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Artikel",
    "correct": "item",
    "choices": [
      "later",
      "thing",
      "cleaning",
      "item"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "auch",
    "correct": "too / also",
    "choices": [
      "equal / whatever",
      "equal",
      "Disco",
      "too / also"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "auf",
    "correct": "on",
    "choices": [
      "experience",
      "on",
      "elevator",
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Auskunft",
    "correct": "information desk",
    "choices": [
      "hunger",
      "information desk",
      "hall",
      "shopping mall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ausland",
    "correct": "foreign country",
    "choices": [
      "job",
      "traffic light",
      "cash register",
      "foreign country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "auf jeden Fall",
    "correct": "definitely",
    "choices": [
      "kiosk",
      "timetable",
      "definitely",
      "sign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "auf keinen Fall",
    "correct": "no way",
    "choices": [
      "problem",
      "photo",
      "no way",
      "class"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "außer",
    "correct": "except",
    "choices": [
      "plan",
      "except",
      "stop",
      "pocket money"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "außerdem",
    "correct": "beside",
    "choices": [
      "still / however / but",
      "beside",
      "angry",
      "difference"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "außerhalb",
    "correct": "outside",
    "choices": [
      "outside",
      "recipe",
      "salary",
      "young"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "aufregend",
    "correct": "exciting",
    "choices": [
      "exciting",
      "in person / even",
      "a lot of",
      "health"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ausstellung",
    "correct": "exhibition",
    "choices": [
      "coat",
      "a few",
      "exhibition",
      "Thank you"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ausweis",
    "correct": "ID card",
    "choices": [
      "private",
      "river",
      "ID card",
      "to bei done (doing sth.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Aufzug",
    "correct": "elevator",
    "choices": [
      "no",
      "elevator",
      "center",
      "job"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Auge",
    "correct": "eye",
    "choices": [
      "opposite",
      "story",
      "definitely",
      "eye"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Auto",
    "correct": "automobile",
    "choices": [
      "automobile",
      "shirt",
      "something",
      "from where"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Autobahn",
    "correct": "Highway",
    "choices": [
      "Highway",
      "soccer",
      "free",
      "for"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Automat",
    "correct": "machine / automat / vending machine",
    "choices": [
      "accurate / exact",
      "machine / automat / vending machine",
      "railway station",
      "opposite"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Baby",
    "correct": "baby",
    "choices": [
      "female colleague / co-worker",
      "baby",
      "game",
      "stove / cooker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Babysitter",
    "correct": "baby-sitter",
    "choices": [
      "baby-sitter",
      "road",
      "everything",
      "occupied"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bei",
    "correct": "at",
    "choices": [
      "next",
      "blond",
      "at",
      "alone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bäckerei",
    "correct": "bakery",
    "choices": [
      "bottle",
      "bakery",
      "foreign country",
      "nobody"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bad",
    "correct": "bath",
    "choices": [
      "pullover",
      "foods / groceries",
      "bath",
      "juice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "beide",
    "correct": "both",
    "choices": [
      "both",
      "by",
      "belly",
      "easy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bahn",
    "correct": "train",
    "choices": [
      "train",
      "as",
      "celebration / feast / party",
      "photo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bekannt",
    "correct": "known",
    "choices": [
      "rest",
      "wish",
      "known",
      "coffee"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bekannte (weiblich)",
    "correct": "female friend / female acquaintance",
    "choices": [
      "female friend / female acquaintance",
      "mouth",
      "engine",
      "thanks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bekannte (männlich)",
    "correct": "male friend / male acquaintance",
    "choices": [
      "comfortable",
      "wedding",
      "male student / pupil",
      "male friend / male acquaintance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bahnhof",
    "correct": "railway station",
    "choices": [
      "before",
      "hospital",
      "railway station",
      "hall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bald",
    "correct": "soon",
    "choices": [
      "soon",
      "competition",
      "all over",
      "lake (pond)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Balkon",
    "correct": "balcony",
    "choices": [
      "by",
      "living room",
      "balcony",
      "exhibition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "beliebt",
    "correct": "popular",
    "choices": [
      "display",
      "accurate / exact",
      "a lot of",
      "popular"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ball",
    "correct": "ball",
    "choices": [
      "park",
      "bath",
      "leisure",
      "ball"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Banane",
    "correct": "banana",
    "choices": [
      "stairway",
      "outside",
      "key",
      "banana"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Band",
    "correct": "(music) band",
    "choices": [
      "human",
      "belly",
      "(music) band",
      "lock / castle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bequem",
    "correct": "comfortable",
    "choices": [
      "comfortable",
      "TRUE",
      "empty",
      "papers, documents"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bank (Geldinstitut)",
    "correct": "Bank (Money Institution)",
    "choices": [
      "camera",
      "mobile",
      "Bank (Money Institution)",
      "new"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bank (Sitzgelegenheit)",
    "correct": "Bank (seating)",
    "choices": [
      "wedding",
      "soccer",
      "Glass",
      "Bank (seating)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Basketball",
    "correct": "basketball",
    "choices": [
      "here",
      "basketball",
      "translation",
      "lots"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Berg",
    "correct": "mountain",
    "choices": [
      "item",
      "total",
      "mountain",
      "thing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bauch",
    "correct": "belly",
    "choices": [
      "small",
      "belly",
      "glad",
      "music"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Beruf",
    "correct": "job",
    "choices": [
      "job",
      "suitcase",
      "which one",
      "urgent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "berühmt",
    "correct": "famous",
    "choices": [
      "be off",
      "earlier",
      "to have an appointment",
      "famous"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Baum",
    "correct": "tree",
    "choices": [
      "tree",
      "on",
      "back",
      "immediately"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bescheid",
    "correct": "answer / decision / information",
    "choices": [
      "anxiety / fear",
      "all",
      "basketball",
      "answer / decision / information"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Baustelle",
    "correct": "Building site / construction site",
    "choices": [
      "project",
      "contract",
      "oil",
      "Building site / construction site"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "besetzt",
    "correct": "occupied",
    "choices": [
      "colorful",
      "Help",
      "eye",
      "occupied"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "besonders",
    "correct": "especially",
    "choices": [
      "especially",
      "outside",
      "time / mark",
      "room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bleistift",
    "correct": "pencil",
    "choices": [
      "train",
      "pencil",
      "radio",
      "first"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "blöd",
    "correct": "stupid",
    "choices": [
      "feels sorry for (so.) / feels sorry about (sth.)",
      "opposite",
      "stupid",
      "sugar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "blond",
    "correct": "blond",
    "choices": [
      "blond",
      "fan",
      "health",
      "noodle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Blog",
    "correct": "blog",
    "choices": [
      "blog",
      "for",
      "heavy",
      "mobile phone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Blume",
    "correct": "flower",
    "choices": [
      "basement, cellar",
      "flower",
      "wind",
      "out / afield"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bluse",
    "correct": "blouse",
    "choices": [
      "blouse",
      "TRUE",
      "password",
      "smart"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bohne",
    "correct": "Bean",
    "choices": [
      "as",
      "drug",
      "library",
      "Bean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "böse",
    "correct": "angry",
    "choices": [
      "vegetables",
      "great",
      "angry",
      "application / canditature"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Besuch",
    "correct": "visit",
    "choices": [
      "title",
      "pause",
      "visit",
      "bird"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bett",
    "correct": "bed",
    "choices": [
      "earlier",
      "bed",
      "spoon",
      "light"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bewerbung",
    "correct": "application / canditature",
    "choices": [
      "except",
      "capital",
      "application / canditature",
      "heater"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Brief",
    "correct": "letter",
    "choices": [
      "hunger",
      "hamburger",
      "tennis",
      "letter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bewölkt",
    "correct": "cloudy",
    "choices": [
      "cloudy",
      "stress",
      "beside",
      "comic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Briefmarke",
    "correct": "Stamp",
    "choices": [
      "medium",
      "before",
      "Stamp",
      "thing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Brille",
    "correct": "glasses",
    "choices": [
      "female tourist",
      "beside",
      "glasses",
      "flat / appartment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bibliothek",
    "correct": "library",
    "choices": [
      "sea",
      "head",
      "because",
      "library"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Brot",
    "correct": "bread",
    "choices": [
      "bread",
      "opposite",
      "pot",
      "noodle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bier",
    "correct": "beer",
    "choices": [
      "beer",
      "information desk",
      "everything",
      "spoon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bild",
    "correct": "image",
    "choices": [
      "image",
      "internship",
      "certificate / school report",
      "sausage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Brücke",
    "correct": "bridge",
    "choices": [
      "colorful",
      "bridge",
      "sharp",
      "contact"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Birne",
    "correct": "pear",
    "choices": [
      "pear",
      "bedroom",
      "shopping mall",
      "fruit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Buch",
    "correct": "book",
    "choices": [
      "display",
      "book",
      "cream",
      "Arrival"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bis",
    "correct": "to",
    "choices": [
      "to",
      "fan",
      "light",
      "museum"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Buchstabe",
    "correct": "letter / character",
    "choices": [
      "smart",
      "letter / character",
      "cold",
      "then"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bitte",
    "correct": "to request (sth.) / to beg for (sth.)",
    "choices": [
      "again",
      "sentence",
      "to request (sth.) / to beg for (sth.)",
      "to be up"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bitte",
    "correct": "Request / Appeal / You're welcome",
    "choices": [
      "wedding",
      "in front",
      "trousers",
      "Request / Appeal / You're welcome"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bunt",
    "correct": "colorful",
    "choices": [
      "colorful",
      "next door",
      "light",
      "movie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bitter",
    "correct": "bitter",
    "choices": [
      "bitter",
      "cleaning",
      "pear",
      "smart"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Büro",
    "correct": "office",
    "choices": [
      "unemployed",
      "office",
      "Youth (female)",
      "leisure"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Blatt",
    "correct": "sheet",
    "choices": [
      "market",
      "sheet",
      "the only child",
      "weather"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bus",
    "correct": "bus",
    "choices": [
      "quiet",
      "bus",
      "male colleague / co-worker",
      "club"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Butter",
    "correct": "butter",
    "choices": [
      "breakfast",
      "butter",
      "from",
      "bright"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Café",
    "correct": "Coffee shop",
    "choices": [
      "female friend / female acquaintance",
      "to",
      "poor",
      "Coffee shop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Cafeteria",
    "correct": "cafeteria",
    "choices": [
      "bottle",
      "cafeteria",
      "towel",
      "Luggage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Datum",
    "correct": "date",
    "choices": [
      "ahead / in front",
      "interview",
      "museum",
      "date"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Chef",
    "correct": "male boss",
    "choices": [
      "driver's license",
      "male boss",
      "occupied",
      "real"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Chefin",
    "correct": "female boss",
    "choices": [
      "Fashion",
      "female boss",
      "center",
      "for example"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Club",
    "correct": "club",
    "choices": [
      "guidance / leadership / conducted tour",
      "thin",
      "tooth",
      "club"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Comic",
    "correct": "comic",
    "choices": [
      "landlady",
      "comic",
      "union / club",
      "at"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "denn",
    "correct": "because",
    "choices": [
      "clearly / obvious",
      "because",
      "a lot of",
      "team"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "deshalb",
    "correct": "therefore / that's why",
    "choices": [
      "therefore / that's why",
      "cloths / outfit",
      "male pensioner",
      "short"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Computer",
    "correct": "computer",
    "choices": [
      "piece",
      "friend, boyfriend",
      "computer",
      "world"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Creme",
    "correct": "cream",
    "choices": [
      "fan",
      "interesting",
      "cream",
      "sometimes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dick",
    "correct": "thick",
    "choices": [
      "thick",
      "location",
      "why",
      "department store"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ding",
    "correct": "thing",
    "choices": [
      "to",
      "cap",
      "music",
      "thing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "direkt",
    "correct": "directly",
    "choices": [
      "male student / pupil",
      "directly",
      "yes",
      "letter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "da",
    "correct": "there",
    "choices": [
      "female friend / female acquaintance",
      "pharmacy",
      "machine / automat / vending machine",
      "there"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Disco",
    "correct": "Disco",
    "choices": [
      "ticket",
      "suitcase",
      "star",
      "Disco"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dabei sein",
    "correct": "to be present / to be there",
    "choices": [
      "hotel",
      "warm",
      "expertise",
      "to be present / to be there"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "darüber",
    "correct": "about that",
    "choices": [
      "about that",
      "flight",
      "music",
      "job"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "doch",
    "correct": "still / however / but",
    "choices": [
      "still / however / but",
      "travel guide",
      "where",
      "sharp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "darauf",
    "correct": "afterwards / after that / thereon",
    "choices": [
      "TV",
      "Help",
      "afterwards / after that / thereon",
      "thanks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dagegen sein",
    "correct": "be against",
    "choices": [
      "be against",
      "exit",
      "different",
      "talk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dafür sein",
    "correct": "to be for it",
    "choices": [
      "good",
      "island",
      "famous",
      "to be for it"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "damals",
    "correct": "back then",
    "choices": [
      "oil",
      "back then",
      "man",
      "from where"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Doppelzimmer",
    "correct": "double room",
    "choices": [
      "lamp",
      "bedroom",
      "double room",
      "so"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dame",
    "correct": "lady",
    "choices": [
      "fever",
      "thence / from there",
      "something",
      "lady"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dank",
    "correct": "thanks",
    "choices": [
      "furniture",
      "Fashion",
      "nobody",
      "thanks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dorf",
    "correct": "village",
    "choices": [
      "youth hostel",
      "signature",
      "village",
      "fruit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dort",
    "correct": "there",
    "choices": [
      "program",
      "soft",
      "link",
      "there"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dorther",
    "correct": "thence / from there",
    "choices": [
      "Boy",
      "pot",
      "thence / from there",
      "poster"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dorthin",
    "correct": "to there",
    "choices": [
      "bed",
      "more",
      "to there",
      "wet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "danke",
    "correct": "Thank you",
    "choices": [
      "rental fee",
      "restaurant",
      "to be on",
      "Thank you"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dann",
    "correct": "then",
    "choices": [
      "wedding",
      "by",
      "jacket",
      "then"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dringend",
    "correct": "urgent",
    "choices": [
      "company",
      "absolutely",
      "urgent",
      "rubbish"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dass",
    "correct": "that",
    "choices": [
      "that",
      "soccer",
      "timetable",
      "free"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Datei",
    "correct": "file",
    "choices": [
      "Jeans",
      "bird",
      "file",
      "plane"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Einkaufszentrum",
    "correct": "shopping mall",
    "choices": [
      "at",
      "holiday",
      "workshop",
      "shopping mall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Drucker",
    "correct": "printer",
    "choices": [
      "immediately",
      "to there",
      "male customer",
      "printer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dumm",
    "correct": "stupid",
    "choices": [
      "mostly",
      "stupid",
      "instrument",
      "foreign country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dunkel",
    "correct": "dark",
    "choices": [
      "dark",
      "tablet",
      "tired",
      "small"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Einladung",
    "correct": "invitation",
    "choices": [
      "leisure",
      "invitation",
      "sharp",
      "Bye-bye! / Cheers!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "einmal",
    "correct": "once",
    "choices": [
      "once",
      "room",
      "empty",
      "then"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dünn",
    "correct": "thin",
    "choices": [
      "ring",
      "thin",
      "pot",
      "thriller"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "durch",
    "correct": "by",
    "choices": [
      "course",
      "by",
      "brochure",
      "computer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Durst",
    "correct": "thirst",
    "choices": [
      "guitar",
      "thirst",
      "stupid",
      "unfortunately"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dusche",
    "correct": "shower",
    "choices": [
      "ring",
      "inexpensive",
      "(music) band",
      "shower"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Eintritt",
    "correct": "entry",
    "choices": [
      "island",
      "entry",
      "Youth (female)",
      "place of birth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "einverstanden sein",
    "correct": "to agree",
    "choices": [
      "travel agency",
      "where",
      "to agree",
      "Coffee shop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "E-Book",
    "correct": "E-Book",
    "choices": [
      "job",
      "behind",
      "price",
      "E-Book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Einzelkind",
    "correct": "the only child",
    "choices": [
      "notebook",
      "when / if",
      "left",
      "the only child"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Einzelzimmer",
    "correct": "single room",
    "choices": [
      "kiosk",
      "expertise",
      "single room",
      "full"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "echt",
    "correct": "real",
    "choices": [
      "message",
      "world",
      "railway station",
      "real"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ecke",
    "correct": "corner",
    "choices": [
      "corner",
      "living room",
      "all / quite",
      "healthy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "egal",
    "correct": "equal / whatever",
    "choices": [
      "interest",
      "equal / whatever",
      "face",
      "music"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Eis",
    "correct": "ice cream",
    "choices": [
      "university",
      "consultation hour",
      "museum",
      "ice cream"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "E-Mail",
    "correct": "e-mail",
    "choices": [
      "tennis",
      "kitchen",
      "seminar / workshop",
      "e-mail"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ehefrau",
    "correct": "wife",
    "choices": [
      "wife",
      "chain",
      "stove / cooker",
      "Arrival"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ehepartner",
    "correct": "spouse",
    "choices": [
      "thin",
      "shirt",
      "normal",
      "spouse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ehemann",
    "correct": "husband",
    "choices": [
      "strange",
      "milk",
      "husband",
      "real"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ei",
    "correct": "egg",
    "choices": [
      "egg",
      "flower",
      "times",
      "order"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "eigenes",
    "correct": "own",
    "choices": [
      "earlier",
      "own",
      "easy",
      "juice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Empfänger",
    "correct": "receiver",
    "choices": [
      "receiver",
      "credit",
      "perfume",
      "ice cream"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ende",
    "correct": "the End",
    "choices": [
      "someone",
      "the End",
      "here",
      "for example"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "einfach",
    "correct": "easy",
    "choices": [
      "flea market",
      "easy",
      "piano",
      "in"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "eng",
    "correct": "tight / narrow / cramped",
    "choices": [
      "outside",
      "tight / narrow / cramped",
      "the only child",
      "recipe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Eingang",
    "correct": "entrance",
    "choices": [
      "entrance",
      "country",
      "idea",
      "landlady"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "einige",
    "correct": "some",
    "choices": [
      "sentence",
      "tight / narrow / cramped",
      "recipe",
      "some"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Entschuldigung",
    "correct": "excuse / apology",
    "choices": [
      "Call",
      "plane",
      "excuse / apology",
      "connection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Erdgeschoss",
    "correct": "ground floor",
    "choices": [
      "ice cream",
      "above / about",
      "drug",
      "ground floor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "falsch",
    "correct": "not correct / wrong",
    "choices": [
      "lemon",
      "pain",
      "not correct / wrong",
      "trip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Erfahrung",
    "correct": "experience",
    "choices": [
      "youth hostel",
      "experience",
      "that",
      "bath"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Familie",
    "correct": "family",
    "choices": [
      "beautiful",
      "beef",
      "therefore / that's why",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Familienname",
    "correct": "family name",
    "choices": [
      "joke",
      "anxiety / fear",
      "family name",
      "snow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "erkältet sein",
    "correct": "to have a cold",
    "choices": [
      "problem",
      "to have a cold",
      "double room",
      "tip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fan",
    "correct": "fan",
    "choices": [
      "poster",
      "after",
      "fan",
      "travel agency"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Farbe",
    "correct": "Colour",
    "choices": [
      "hair",
      "Colour",
      "normal",
      "stove / cooker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "erlaubt sein",
    "correct": "to be allowed",
    "choices": [
      "sports ground",
      "colorful",
      "to be allowed",
      "too / also"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Erlaubnis",
    "correct": "permission",
    "choices": [
      "be against",
      "body",
      "address",
      "permission"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fast",
    "correct": "nearly",
    "choices": [
      "level / floor",
      "pot",
      "nearly",
      "mobile phone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "faul",
    "correct": "lazy",
    "choices": [
      "old",
      "round tour / circut",
      "new",
      "lazy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ermäßigung",
    "correct": "discount",
    "choices": [
      "ring",
      "hobby",
      "rich",
      "discount"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fehler",
    "correct": "error",
    "choices": [
      "drug",
      "festival",
      "error",
      "rubbish"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Feier",
    "correct": "celebration",
    "choices": [
      "off / away",
      "and",
      "education",
      "celebration"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Feierabend",
    "correct": "end of working day",
    "choices": [
      "end of working day",
      "last",
      "stop",
      "for sure"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Feiertag",
    "correct": "holiday",
    "choices": [
      "to have a cold",
      "soccer",
      "holiday",
      "salary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "erst",
    "correct": "first",
    "choices": [
      "animal",
      "cupboard / closet",
      "first",
      "machine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Erwachsene",
    "correct": "adult",
    "choices": [
      "adult",
      "office",
      "password",
      "arm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fenster",
    "correct": "window",
    "choices": [
      "window",
      "juice",
      "desire / delight / lust",
      "arm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fernseher",
    "correct": "TV",
    "choices": [
      "TV",
      "lemon",
      "landlord",
      "forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "etwas",
    "correct": "something",
    "choices": [
      "drug",
      "something",
      "library",
      "offer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fertig sein",
    "correct": "to bei done (doing sth.)",
    "choices": [
      "blog",
      "for",
      "country",
      "to bei done (doing sth.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fest",
    "correct": "celebration / feast / party",
    "choices": [
      "today",
      "soccer",
      "celebration / feast / party",
      "family name"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fach",
    "correct": "subject",
    "choices": [
      "that",
      "subject",
      "angry",
      "package"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Abfahrt",
    "correct": "Departure",
    "choices": [
      "ahead / in front",
      "Departure",
      "sheet",
      "taxi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fahrkarte",
    "correct": "ticket",
    "choices": [
      "ticket",
      "inexpensive",
      "education",
      "age"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Festival",
    "correct": "festival",
    "choices": [
      "papers, documents",
      "festival",
      "internet",
      "guest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fett",
    "correct": "fat",
    "choices": [
      "supermarket",
      "ending / the end",
      "fat",
      "oil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fieber",
    "correct": "fever",
    "choices": [
      "blog",
      "lemon",
      "fever",
      "service"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Film",
    "correct": "movie",
    "choices": [
      "printer",
      "world",
      "language",
      "movie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fahrplan",
    "correct": "timetable",
    "choices": [
      "lemon",
      "on",
      "timetable",
      "sun"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Firma",
    "correct": "company",
    "choices": [
      "company",
      "sentence",
      "sometimes",
      "thanks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fahrrad",
    "correct": "bicycle",
    "choices": [
      "blog",
      "pause",
      "in person / even",
      "bicycle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fit sein",
    "correct": "to be fit",
    "choices": [
      "be off",
      "be against",
      "last",
      "to be fit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Flasche",
    "correct": "bottle",
    "choices": [
      "Sir",
      "bottle",
      "art",
      "celebration / feast / party"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "früher",
    "correct": "earlier",
    "choices": [
      "cloudy",
      "earlier",
      "driver's license",
      "people"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Frühstück",
    "correct": "breakfast",
    "choices": [
      "straight",
      "noisy",
      "breakfast",
      "in / into"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Flohmarkt",
    "correct": "flea market",
    "choices": [
      "accident",
      "seminar / workshop",
      "flea market",
      "all"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Führerschein",
    "correct": "driver's license",
    "choices": [
      "contact",
      "skirt",
      "driver's license",
      "training"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Flug",
    "correct": "flight",
    "choices": [
      "window",
      "flight",
      "urgent",
      "room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Führung",
    "correct": "guidance / leadership / conducted tour",
    "choices": [
      "guidance / leadership / conducted tour",
      "blond",
      "last",
      "sign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Flugzeug",
    "correct": "plane",
    "choices": [
      "colorful",
      "to be for it",
      "hard",
      "plane"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "für",
    "correct": "for",
    "choices": [
      "male pensioner",
      "thriller",
      "plate",
      "for"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fluss",
    "correct": "river",
    "choices": [
      "interest",
      "river",
      "scholarship",
      "nobody"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Formular",
    "correct": "form",
    "choices": [
      "traffic",
      "suitcase",
      "under",
      "form"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fotoapparat",
    "correct": "camera",
    "choices": [
      "camera",
      "thunderstorm",
      "Help",
      "lake (pond)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fuß",
    "correct": "foot",
    "choices": [
      "around",
      "round tour / circut",
      "engine",
      "foot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fußball",
    "correct": "soccer",
    "choices": [
      "toilet",
      "exam",
      "soccer",
      "celebration / feast / party"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Foto",
    "correct": "photo",
    "choices": [
      "or",
      "health insurance",
      "times",
      "photo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Frage",
    "correct": "question",
    "choices": [
      "exciting",
      "page",
      "question",
      "there"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Frau",
    "correct": "Mrs",
    "choices": [
      "language",
      "Mrs",
      "city",
      "opinion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gabel",
    "correct": "fork",
    "choices": [
      "fork",
      "passport",
      "glasses",
      "soon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ganz",
    "correct": "all / quite",
    "choices": [
      "course",
      "bath",
      "equal",
      "all / quite"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Freizeit",
    "correct": "leisure",
    "choices": [
      "theatre",
      "last",
      "leisure",
      "Arrival"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fremd",
    "correct": "strange",
    "choices": [
      "strange",
      "world",
      "male partner",
      "engine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Garage",
    "correct": "garage",
    "choices": [
      "proximity / closeness",
      "garage",
      "great",
      "homepage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gast",
    "correct": "guest",
    "choices": [
      "cloud",
      "poster",
      "address",
      "guest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Geburtstag",
    "correct": "birthday",
    "choices": [
      "display",
      "great",
      "birthday",
      "potato"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Geburtsort",
    "correct": "place of birth",
    "choices": [
      "culture",
      "pear",
      "place of birth",
      "current"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Geburtsjahr",
    "correct": "year of birth",
    "choices": [
      "thick",
      "year of birth",
      "from where",
      "to do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Freund",
    "correct": "friend, boyfriend",
    "choices": [
      "plan",
      "wind",
      "friend, boyfriend",
      "jacket"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Freundin",
    "correct": "female friend, girlfriend",
    "choices": [
      "female friend, girlfriend",
      "foot",
      "product",
      "occupied"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "geehrte",
    "correct": "Dear / honored",
    "choices": [
      "lemon",
      "Dear / honored",
      "milk",
      "nature"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "froh",
    "correct": "glad",
    "choices": [
      "water",
      "glad",
      "Glass",
      "moment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "früh",
    "correct": "early",
    "choices": [
      "blouse",
      "sea",
      "early",
      "sausage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gegenteil",
    "correct": "opposite",
    "choices": [
      "experience",
      "opposite",
      "backpack",
      "male partner"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gegenüber",
    "correct": "across / across from",
    "choices": [
      "pen",
      "river",
      "group",
      "across / across from"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gehalt",
    "correct": "salary",
    "choices": [
      "someone",
      "information desk",
      "salary",
      "basketball"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gewitter",
    "correct": "thunderstorm",
    "choices": [
      "thunderstorm",
      "scissors",
      "therefore / that's why",
      "urgent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gitarre",
    "correct": "guitar",
    "choices": [
      "guitar",
      "interest",
      "bakery",
      "map"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Glas",
    "correct": "Glass",
    "choices": [
      "in person / even",
      "Glass",
      "text",
      "young"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gleich",
    "correct": "equal",
    "choices": [
      "foods / groceries",
      "without",
      "equal",
      "some"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Geld",
    "correct": "money",
    "choices": [
      "money",
      "subject",
      "brochure",
      "consultation hour"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gleis",
    "correct": "track",
    "choices": [
      "company",
      "track",
      "you",
      "which one"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Glück",
    "correct": "happiness",
    "choices": [
      "bedroom",
      "Colour",
      "sick",
      "happiness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Geldbörse",
    "correct": "Purse",
    "choices": [
      "strict",
      "Excursion",
      "Purse",
      "school"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gemüse",
    "correct": "vegetables",
    "choices": [
      "vegetables",
      "money",
      "word",
      "bright"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Glückwunsch",
    "correct": "congratulation",
    "choices": [
      "pen",
      "congratulation",
      "Luggage",
      "mobile phone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "genau",
    "correct": "accurate / exact",
    "choices": [
      "accurate / exact",
      "towel",
      "house",
      "union / club"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "genug",
    "correct": "enough",
    "choices": [
      "cup",
      "enough",
      "without",
      "E-Book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gepäck",
    "correct": "Luggage",
    "choices": [
      "last",
      "desire / delight / lust",
      "post code",
      "Luggage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gerade",
    "correct": "just",
    "choices": [
      "problem",
      "just",
      "volleyball",
      "some"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Grippe",
    "correct": "flu",
    "choices": [
      "on",
      "flu",
      "town hall",
      "to be allowed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "groß",
    "correct": "big",
    "choices": [
      "big",
      "plan",
      "practice",
      "situation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "geradeaus",
    "correct": "straight",
    "choices": [
      "straight",
      "tennis",
      "what",
      "normal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Größe",
    "correct": "size",
    "choices": [
      "comfortable",
      "pig",
      "size",
      "means of transport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gerät",
    "correct": "device",
    "choices": [
      "wife",
      "information",
      "intelligent",
      "device"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gruppe",
    "correct": "group",
    "choices": [
      "number",
      "outside",
      "concert",
      "group"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gericht",
    "correct": "dish",
    "choices": [
      "dish",
      "pear",
      "which one",
      "pig"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gruß",
    "correct": "greeting",
    "choices": [
      "greeting",
      "offer",
      "family name",
      "sport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Geschäft",
    "correct": "shop / business",
    "choices": [
      "ticket",
      "time / mark",
      "shop / business",
      "laptop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gültig sein",
    "correct": "to be valid",
    "choices": [
      "Long",
      "to be valid",
      "driver's license",
      "package"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Geschenk",
    "correct": "present",
    "choices": [
      "present",
      "expertise",
      "education",
      "e-mail"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Geschichte",
    "correct": "story",
    "choices": [
      "off / away",
      "story",
      "light",
      "bath"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Geschirr",
    "correct": "dishes",
    "choices": [
      "language",
      "dishes",
      "website",
      "means of transport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gut",
    "correct": "good",
    "choices": [
      "good",
      "back",
      "magazine",
      "amount"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gesicht",
    "correct": "face",
    "choices": [
      "to",
      "face",
      "rest",
      "body"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gespräch",
    "correct": "talk",
    "choices": [
      "health insurance",
      "registration",
      "to hurt",
      "talk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gesund",
    "correct": "healthy",
    "choices": [
      "healthy",
      "sheet",
      "sometimes",
      "to bei done (doing sth.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gesundheit",
    "correct": "health",
    "choices": [
      "alone",
      "a lot of",
      "sometimes",
      "health"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Getränk",
    "correct": "drink",
    "choices": [
      "drink",
      "female customer",
      "absolutely",
      "mobile phone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Haar",
    "correct": "hair",
    "choices": [
      "end of working day",
      "enough",
      "hair",
      "tired"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Halle",
    "correct": "hall",
    "choices": [
      "program",
      "hall",
      "kiosk",
      "cold"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hallo",
    "correct": "hello",
    "choices": [
      "hello",
      "Help",
      "suit",
      "paper"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "herein",
    "correct": "in / this way in",
    "choices": [
      "slowly",
      "strict",
      "in / this way in",
      "backpack"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hals",
    "correct": "neck",
    "choices": [
      "be off",
      "pig",
      "neck",
      "menu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Herd",
    "correct": "stove / cooker",
    "choices": [
      "thick",
      "from where",
      "nearly",
      "stove / cooker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Herr",
    "correct": "Sir",
    "choices": [
      "Sir",
      "drink",
      "bread",
      "museum"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hamburger",
    "correct": "hamburger",
    "choices": [
      "hamburger",
      "because",
      "hand",
      "for"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Haltestelle",
    "correct": "stop",
    "choices": [
      "someone",
      "pig",
      "stop",
      "lake (pond)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hand",
    "correct": "hand",
    "choices": [
      "hand",
      "both",
      "suit",
      "phone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Handtuch",
    "correct": "towel",
    "choices": [
      "bed",
      "round tour / circut",
      "towel",
      "current"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Handy",
    "correct": "mobile",
    "choices": [
      "female colleague / co-worker",
      "mobile",
      "to there",
      "suit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "heute",
    "correct": "today",
    "choices": [
      "post",
      "today",
      "question",
      "device"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hier",
    "correct": "here",
    "choices": [
      "theatre",
      "Attention!",
      "dear, beloved",
      "here"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hart",
    "correct": "hard",
    "choices": [
      "about that",
      "hard",
      "deep",
      "movie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hilfe",
    "correct": "Help",
    "choices": [
      "all over",
      "at least",
      "Help",
      "sport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hauptstadt",
    "correct": "capital",
    "choices": [
      "police",
      "education",
      "capital",
      "accident"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Himmel",
    "correct": "sky",
    "choices": [
      "trousers",
      "expertise",
      "sky",
      "consultation hour"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Haus",
    "correct": "house",
    "choices": [
      "hall",
      "exhibition",
      "milk",
      "house"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hin",
    "correct": "(to go) there",
    "choices": [
      "Thank you",
      "entry",
      "equal",
      "(to go) there"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hinein",
    "correct": "in / into",
    "choices": [
      "in / into",
      "per",
      "especially",
      "rubbish"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hinaus",
    "correct": "out / afield",
    "choices": [
      "anxiety / fear",
      "piece",
      "out / afield",
      "full"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Haushalt",
    "correct": "household",
    "choices": [
      "because",
      "horse",
      "household",
      "eye"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hinter",
    "correct": "behind",
    "choices": [
      "small",
      "therefore / that's why",
      "behind",
      "for sure"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Heft",
    "correct": "notebook",
    "choices": [
      "animal",
      "notebook",
      "stress",
      "talk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Heimat",
    "correct": "homeland",
    "choices": [
      "university",
      "signature",
      "homeland",
      "rest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hobby",
    "correct": "hobby",
    "choices": [
      "both",
      "hobby",
      "tight / narrow / cramped",
      "traffic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hoch",
    "correct": "high",
    "choices": [
      "someone",
      "as",
      "at least",
      "high"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hochzeit",
    "correct": "wedding",
    "choices": [
      "wedding",
      "program / show / broadcast",
      "rest",
      "sun"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "heiß",
    "correct": "hot",
    "choices": [
      "guitar",
      "strict",
      "hot",
      "E-Book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Heizung",
    "correct": "heater",
    "choices": [
      "strange",
      "equal / whatever",
      "fat",
      "heater"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Homepage",
    "correct": "homepage",
    "choices": [
      "sea",
      "to be away",
      "place",
      "homepage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hell",
    "correct": "bright",
    "choices": [
      "hunger",
      "wife",
      "when / if",
      "bright"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hose",
    "correct": "trousers",
    "choices": [
      "trousers",
      "human",
      "lock / castle",
      "sentence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hemd",
    "correct": "shirt",
    "choices": [
      "egg",
      "certificate / school report",
      "shirt",
      "glad"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "heraus",
    "correct": "out",
    "choices": [
      "course",
      "out",
      "fork",
      "beautiful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hotel",
    "correct": "hotel",
    "choices": [
      "hotel",
      "oil",
      "sun",
      "movie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hund",
    "correct": "dog",
    "choices": [
      "Highway",
      "dog",
      "circus",
      "poster"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hunger",
    "correct": "hunger",
    "choices": [
      "hunger",
      "living room",
      "program / show / broadcast",
      "behind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Idee",
    "correct": "idea",
    "choices": [
      "umbrella",
      "man",
      "slowly",
      "idea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "jung",
    "correct": "young",
    "choices": [
      "to",
      "otherwise",
      "Request / Appeal / You're welcome",
      "young"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Junge",
    "correct": "Boy",
    "choices": [
      "Boy",
      "subject",
      "horse",
      "aim / target"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "in",
    "correct": "in",
    "choices": [
      "price",
      "basketball",
      "equal",
      "in"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Information",
    "correct": "information",
    "choices": [
      "problem",
      "information",
      "homeland",
      "Purse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kaffee",
    "correct": "coffee",
    "choices": [
      "hunger",
      "nearly",
      "Departure",
      "coffee"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kalender",
    "correct": "calendar",
    "choices": [
      "calendar",
      "be off",
      "equal / whatever",
      "age"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kalt",
    "correct": "cold",
    "choices": [
      "cold",
      "by",
      "off / away",
      "mobile phone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Insel",
    "correct": "island",
    "choices": [
      "vegetables",
      "be against",
      "island",
      "last"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Instrument",
    "correct": "instrument",
    "choices": [
      "out",
      "instrument",
      "school",
      "engine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "intelligent",
    "correct": "intelligent",
    "choices": [
      "beer",
      "perfume",
      "intelligent",
      "medium"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kamera",
    "correct": "camera",
    "choices": [
      "camera",
      "course",
      "a few",
      "fridge"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Interesse",
    "correct": "interest",
    "choices": [
      "interest",
      "congratulation",
      "directly",
      "tip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kaputt",
    "correct": "broken",
    "choices": [
      "broken",
      "behind",
      "mouth",
      "lots"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Karte",
    "correct": "map",
    "choices": [
      "exciting",
      "in person / even",
      "map",
      "Building site / construction site"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "interessant",
    "correct": "interesting",
    "choices": [
      "interesting",
      "product",
      "address",
      "bird"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "international",
    "correct": "international",
    "choices": [
      "on-line",
      "pause",
      "international",
      "question"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Internet",
    "correct": "internet",
    "choices": [
      "strange",
      "pig",
      "interview",
      "internet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kartoffel",
    "correct": "potato",
    "choices": [
      "from where",
      "lemon",
      "potato",
      "answer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Käse",
    "correct": "cheese",
    "choices": [
      "job",
      "Long",
      "answer",
      "cheese"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kasse",
    "correct": "cash register",
    "choices": [
      "cash register",
      "village",
      "suitcase",
      "current"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Katze",
    "correct": "cat",
    "choices": [
      "kitchen",
      "cat",
      "center",
      "sign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Interview",
    "correct": "interview",
    "choices": [
      "credit",
      "interview",
      "package",
      "driver's license"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kaufhaus",
    "correct": "department store",
    "choices": [
      "fair",
      "(music) band",
      "contract",
      "department store"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kein",
    "correct": "no / none",
    "choices": [
      "cap",
      "lemon",
      "no / none",
      "occupied"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ja",
    "correct": "yes",
    "choices": [
      "subject / topic",
      "cloud",
      "yes",
      "mobile phone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jacke",
    "correct": "jacket",
    "choices": [
      "mostly",
      "bad / worst / upsetting",
      "which one",
      "jacket"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jeans",
    "correct": "Jeans",
    "choices": [
      "Jeans",
      "capital",
      "Beginning",
      "as"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Keller",
    "correct": "basement, cellar",
    "choices": [
      "basement, cellar",
      "human",
      "pear",
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "jedes",
    "correct": "each",
    "choices": [
      "thin",
      "cafeteria",
      "pill / tablet",
      "each"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "jemand",
    "correct": "someone",
    "choices": [
      "someone",
      "door",
      "country",
      "poster"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "jetzt",
    "correct": "now",
    "choices": [
      "now",
      "fridge",
      "library",
      "weather"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Job",
    "correct": "job",
    "choices": [
      "job",
      "present",
      "clearly / obvious",
      "portion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kenntnisse",
    "correct": "expertise",
    "choices": [
      "expertise",
      "interesting",
      "homeland",
      "to agree"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kette",
    "correct": "chain",
    "choices": [
      "chain",
      "star",
      "age",
      "tip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jugendherberge",
    "correct": "youth hostel",
    "choices": [
      "youth hostel",
      "congratulation",
      "good",
      "(to go) there"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kind",
    "correct": "child",
    "choices": [
      "child",
      "oil",
      "piano",
      "occupied"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jugendliche (männlich)",
    "correct": "Youth (male)",
    "choices": [
      "subject",
      "path",
      "Youth (male)",
      "connection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jugendliche (weiblich)",
    "correct": "Youth (female)",
    "choices": [
      "baby",
      "back",
      "Youth (female)",
      "bright"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kino",
    "correct": "movie theater",
    "choices": [
      "company",
      "lemon",
      "directly",
      "movie theater"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kiosk",
    "correct": "kiosk",
    "choices": [
      "kiosk",
      "letter / character",
      "(music) band",
      "unfortunately"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kirche",
    "correct": "church",
    "choices": [
      "train",
      "church",
      "market",
      "a pity"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kostenlos",
    "correct": "free",
    "choices": [
      "traffic",
      "free",
      "afterwards / after that / thereon",
      "knife"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "krank",
    "correct": "sick",
    "choices": [
      "stress",
      "text",
      "sick",
      "rubbish"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Krankenhaus",
    "correct": "hospital",
    "choices": [
      "lady",
      "in person / even",
      "pill / tablet",
      "hospital"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "klar",
    "correct": "clearly / obvious",
    "choices": [
      "pharmacy",
      "clearly / obvious",
      "star",
      "map"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Krankenkasse",
    "correct": "health insurance",
    "choices": [
      "health insurance",
      "church",
      "rich",
      "to bei done (doing sth.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Krankheit",
    "correct": "illness",
    "choices": [
      "TV",
      "at",
      "illness",
      "bright"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kredit",
    "correct": "credit",
    "choices": [
      "credit",
      "radio",
      "lemon",
      "pool"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Klavier",
    "correct": "piano",
    "choices": [
      "dishes",
      "human",
      "to be up",
      "piano"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kleid",
    "correct": "dress",
    "choices": [
      "dress",
      "definitely",
      "eye",
      "ice cream"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kreuzung",
    "correct": "crossing",
    "choices": [
      "crossing",
      "on",
      "education",
      "letter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kleidung",
    "correct": "cloths / outfit",
    "choices": [
      "flea market",
      "excuse / apology",
      "Disco",
      "cloths / outfit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "klein",
    "correct": "small",
    "choices": [
      "small",
      "movie theater",
      "different",
      "Bank (seating)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Krimi",
    "correct": "thriller",
    "choices": [
      "thriller",
      "cheese",
      "hospital",
      "cloths / outfit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "klug",
    "correct": "smart",
    "choices": [
      "smart",
      "total",
      "pear",
      "towel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Küche",
    "correct": "kitchen",
    "choices": [
      "Beginning",
      "kitchen",
      "afterwards / after that / thereon",
      "active"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kühl",
    "correct": "cool",
    "choices": [
      "sea",
      "under",
      "cool",
      "grade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Koffer",
    "correct": "suitcase",
    "choices": [
      "shopping mall",
      "calendar",
      "suitcase",
      "in"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kühlschrank",
    "correct": "fridge",
    "choices": [
      "garage",
      "fridge",
      "male student / pupil",
      "lamp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kollege",
    "correct": "male colleague / co-worker",
    "choices": [
      "pizza",
      "male colleague / co-worker",
      "Clock",
      "lots"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kollegin",
    "correct": "female colleague / co-worker",
    "choices": [
      "female colleague / co-worker",
      "guitar",
      "intelligent",
      "meeting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kultur",
    "correct": "culture",
    "choices": [
      "culture",
      "back",
      "pear",
      "sharp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kunde",
    "correct": "male customer",
    "choices": [
      "egg",
      "more",
      "male customer",
      "to bei done (doing sth.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kundin",
    "correct": "female customer",
    "choices": [
      "basement, cellar",
      "mineral water",
      "point of interest",
      "female customer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kunst",
    "correct": "art",
    "choices": [
      "art",
      "certificate / school report",
      "household",
      "switch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kontakt",
    "correct": "contact",
    "choices": [
      "employee",
      "child",
      "equal",
      "contact"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Konto",
    "correct": "account",
    "choices": [
      "account",
      "hair",
      "who",
      "when / if"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kurs",
    "correct": "course",
    "choices": [
      "course",
      "letter / character",
      "interview",
      "female student"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kurz",
    "correct": "short",
    "choices": [
      "short",
      "stress",
      "cream",
      "idea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Konzert",
    "correct": "concert",
    "choices": [
      "living room",
      "concert",
      "celebration",
      "female neighbor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kopf",
    "correct": "head",
    "choices": [
      "quality",
      "head",
      "whiteboard",
      "no / none"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Körper",
    "correct": "body",
    "choices": [
      "chain",
      "sweet",
      "body",
      "cup"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lampe",
    "correct": "lamp",
    "choices": [
      "blouse",
      "even",
      "lamp",
      "sports ground"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Land",
    "correct": "country",
    "choices": [
      "sea",
      "(music) band",
      "country",
      "place"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Kosmetik",
    "correct": "cosmetics",
    "choices": [
      "cosmetics",
      "TV",
      "to there",
      "engine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lang",
    "correct": "long",
    "choices": [
      "ticket",
      "especially",
      "chain",
      "long"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lange",
    "correct": "Long",
    "choices": [
      "youth hostel",
      "Long",
      "practice",
      "more"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "langsam",
    "correct": "slowly",
    "choices": [
      "park",
      "slowly",
      "tip",
      "volleyball"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Link",
    "correct": "link",
    "choices": [
      "which one",
      "cheese",
      "link",
      "photo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "links",
    "correct": "left",
    "choices": [
      "Sir",
      "end of working day",
      "accident",
      "left"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Löffel",
    "correct": "spoon",
    "choices": [
      "window",
      "equal / whatever",
      "spoon",
      "ice cream"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lokal",
    "correct": "pub / tavern / restaurant",
    "choices": [
      "pub / tavern / restaurant",
      "bad / worst / upsetting",
      "track",
      "holiday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lüge",
    "correct": "lie",
    "choices": [
      "lie",
      "year of birth",
      "desire / delight / lust",
      "book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Laptop",
    "correct": "laptop",
    "choices": [
      "connection",
      "(to go) there",
      "rental fee",
      "laptop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lust",
    "correct": "desire / delight / lust",
    "choices": [
      "some",
      "sweet",
      "wish",
      "desire / delight / lust"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "laut",
    "correct": "noisy",
    "choices": [
      "noisy",
      "child",
      "error",
      "laptop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lebensmittel",
    "correct": "foods / groceries",
    "choices": [
      "foods / groceries",
      "union / club",
      "to hurt",
      "village"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "leer",
    "correct": "empty",
    "choices": [
      "studies / academic studies",
      "strict",
      "empty",
      "intelligent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "leicht",
    "correct": "light",
    "choices": [
      "money",
      "dishes",
      "wine",
      "light"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "leider",
    "correct": "unfortunately",
    "choices": [
      "fruit",
      "oil",
      "unfortunately",
      "there"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "leidtun",
    "correct": "feels sorry for (so.) / feels sorry about (sth.)",
    "choices": [
      "feels sorry for (so.) / feels sorry about (sth.)",
      "error",
      "menu",
      "plane"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mailbox",
    "correct": "mailbox",
    "choices": [
      "mailbox",
      "cat",
      "workshop",
      "female student"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mal",
    "correct": "times",
    "choices": [
      "job",
      "Help",
      "equal / whatever",
      "times"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mal",
    "correct": "time / mark",
    "choices": [
      "coat",
      "time / mark",
      "scholarship",
      "greeting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "man",
    "correct": "you",
    "choices": [
      "mailbox",
      "rose",
      "you",
      "plane"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "leise",
    "correct": "quiet",
    "choices": [
      "quiet",
      "skirt",
      "in / this way in",
      "thick"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "manche",
    "correct": "some",
    "choices": [
      "bus",
      "invitation",
      "some",
      "bad / poor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "manchmal",
    "correct": "sometimes",
    "choices": [
      "round tour / circut",
      "next door",
      "sometimes",
      "bright"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mann",
    "correct": "man",
    "choices": [
      "Fashion",
      "holiday",
      "cool",
      "man"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "letzte",
    "correct": "last",
    "choices": [
      "landlady",
      "last",
      "cap",
      "guest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mantel",
    "correct": "coat",
    "choices": [
      "coat",
      "round tour / circut",
      "male colleague / co-worker",
      "absolutely"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Markt",
    "correct": "market",
    "choices": [
      "male tourist",
      "market",
      "tip",
      "all"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Leute",
    "correct": "people",
    "choices": [
      "egg",
      "floor",
      "people",
      "male tourist"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Licht",
    "correct": "light",
    "choices": [
      "female pensioner",
      "after",
      "to be away",
      "light"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lieber",
    "correct": "dear, beloved",
    "choices": [
      "stairway",
      "traffic light",
      "dear, beloved",
      "butter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Maschine",
    "correct": "machine",
    "choices": [
      "machine",
      "tooth",
      "pocket money",
      "computer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Medikament",
    "correct": "drug",
    "choices": [
      "again",
      "bed",
      "hamburger",
      "drug"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Meer",
    "correct": "sea",
    "choices": [
      "sea",
      "great",
      "sugar",
      "across / across from"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lieblingsfarbe",
    "correct": "favourite colour",
    "choices": [
      "healthy",
      "shoe",
      "course",
      "favourite colour"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mehr",
    "correct": "more",
    "choices": [
      "pen",
      "more",
      "page",
      "time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lied",
    "correct": "song",
    "choices": [
      "ring",
      "present",
      "song",
      "where"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Meinung",
    "correct": "opinion",
    "choices": [
      "last",
      "lemon",
      "opinion",
      "department store"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "meistens",
    "correct": "mostly",
    "choices": [
      "mostly",
      "horse",
      "when / if",
      "track"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Menge",
    "correct": "amount",
    "choices": [
      "sausage",
      "flea market",
      "world",
      "amount"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mensch",
    "correct": "human",
    "choices": [
      "female tourist",
      "human",
      "quiz",
      "laptop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Moment",
    "correct": "moment",
    "choices": [
      "song",
      "page",
      "to request (sth.) / to beg for (sth.)",
      "moment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Motor",
    "correct": "engine",
    "choices": [
      "registration",
      "lamp",
      "city",
      "engine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Motorroller",
    "correct": "scooter",
    "choices": [
      "scooter",
      "in / into",
      "comfortable",
      "sport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "müde",
    "correct": "tired",
    "choices": [
      "bus",
      "talk",
      "tired",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Müll",
    "correct": "rubbish",
    "choices": [
      "strict",
      "offer",
      "female student",
      "rubbish"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Messe",
    "correct": "fair",
    "choices": [
      "fair",
      "number",
      "exhibition",
      "no / none"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Messer",
    "correct": "knife",
    "choices": [
      "key",
      "enough",
      "bicycle",
      "knife"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Miete",
    "correct": "rental fee",
    "choices": [
      "nobody",
      "cap",
      "tip",
      "rental fee"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mund",
    "correct": "mouth",
    "choices": [
      "hard",
      "mouth",
      "program / show / broadcast",
      "man"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Museum",
    "correct": "museum",
    "choices": [
      "line / row / queue",
      "female tourist",
      "umbrella",
      "museum"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Musik",
    "correct": "music",
    "choices": [
      "and",
      "age",
      "where",
      "music"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Milch",
    "correct": "milk",
    "choices": [
      "Call",
      "restaurant",
      "milk",
      "Building site / construction site"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mindestens",
    "correct": "at least",
    "choices": [
      "pub / tavern / restaurant",
      "to be",
      "at least",
      "urgent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mütze",
    "correct": "cap",
    "choices": [
      "small",
      "ball",
      "cap",
      "happiness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mineralwasser",
    "correct": "mineral water",
    "choices": [
      "university",
      "male boss",
      "mineral water",
      "class"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nach",
    "correct": "after",
    "choices": [
      "after",
      "on",
      "rice",
      "town hall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mit",
    "correct": "with",
    "choices": [
      "hamburger",
      "comic",
      "with",
      "rose"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Nachbarin",
    "correct": "female neighbor",
    "choices": [
      "landlady",
      "illness",
      "banana",
      "female neighbor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Nachricht",
    "correct": "message",
    "choices": [
      "message",
      "island",
      "file",
      "plane"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nächste",
    "correct": "next",
    "choices": [
      "next",
      "dress",
      "urgent",
      "to bei done (doing sth.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mitarbeiter",
    "correct": "employee",
    "choices": [
      "employee",
      "after",
      "living room",
      "program / show / broadcast"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Nähe",
    "correct": "proximity / closeness",
    "choices": [
      "proximity / closeness",
      "thing",
      "foreign country",
      "to be on"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mitte",
    "correct": "center",
    "choices": [
      "to",
      "to be up",
      "center",
      "banana"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Name",
    "correct": "name",
    "choices": [
      "plant",
      "international",
      "name",
      "when"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mittel",
    "correct": "medium",
    "choices": [
      "far",
      "at least",
      "medium",
      "therefore / that's why"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nass",
    "correct": "wet",
    "choices": [
      "thunderstorm",
      "celebration / feast / party",
      "wet",
      "size"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Möbel",
    "correct": "furniture",
    "choices": [
      "furniture",
      "salad",
      "volleyball",
      "yes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mobiltelefon",
    "correct": "mobile phone",
    "choices": [
      "map / city map",
      "pocket money",
      "lady",
      "mobile phone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Natur",
    "correct": "nature",
    "choices": [
      "female pensioner",
      "sentence",
      "alone",
      "nature"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mode",
    "correct": "Fashion",
    "choices": [
      "Fashion",
      "age",
      "as",
      "shopping mall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nebenan",
    "correct": "next door",
    "choices": [
      "Boy",
      "how much",
      "next door",
      "dead"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nein",
    "correct": "no",
    "choices": [
      "no",
      "with",
      "female customer",
      "sick"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ohne",
    "correct": "without",
    "choices": [
      "all over",
      "answer",
      "without",
      "banana"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nervös",
    "correct": "nervous",
    "choices": [
      "nervous",
      "visit",
      "beach",
      "place of birth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nett",
    "correct": "kind",
    "choices": [
      "kind",
      "enough",
      "visit",
      "some"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ohr",
    "correct": "ear",
    "choices": [
      "water",
      "egg",
      "single room",
      "ear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Öl",
    "correct": "oil",
    "choices": [
      "comfortable",
      "homeland",
      "river",
      "oil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "neu",
    "correct": "new",
    "choices": [
      "on",
      "shirt",
      "talk",
      "new"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "online",
    "correct": "on-line",
    "choices": [
      "off / away",
      "on-line",
      "sports ground",
      "place"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nichts",
    "correct": "nothing",
    "choices": [
      "note",
      "all / quite",
      "the only child",
      "nothing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Orange",
    "correct": "orange",
    "choices": [
      "continue",
      "mineral water",
      "tram",
      "orange"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ordnung",
    "correct": "order",
    "choices": [
      "quality",
      "internet",
      "to",
      "order"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "niemand",
    "correct": "nobody",
    "choices": [
      "nervous",
      "fork",
      "male tourist",
      "nobody"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nirgends",
    "correct": "nowhere",
    "choices": [
      "dish",
      "wedding",
      "female customer",
      "nowhere"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ort",
    "correct": "place",
    "choices": [
      "Coffee shop",
      "studies / academic studies",
      "each",
      "place"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "noch",
    "correct": "still",
    "choices": [
      "line / row / queue",
      "still",
      "bitter",
      "idea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "normal",
    "correct": "normal",
    "choices": [
      "reception",
      "to do",
      "single room",
      "normal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Note",
    "correct": "grade",
    "choices": [
      "cloths / outfit",
      "expensive",
      "across / across from",
      "grade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Notiz",
    "correct": "note",
    "choices": [
      "note",
      "over / past",
      "wet",
      "answer / decision / information"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Paar",
    "correct": "Pair",
    "choices": [
      "Building site / construction site",
      "over / past",
      "arm",
      "Pair"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ein paar",
    "correct": "a few",
    "choices": [
      "noisy",
      "a few",
      "to whom / to who",
      "suitcase"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Nudel",
    "correct": "noodle",
    "choices": [
      "angry",
      "different",
      "from where",
      "noodle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Nummer",
    "correct": "number",
    "choices": [
      "number",
      "title",
      "market",
      "flea market"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Paket",
    "correct": "package",
    "choices": [
      "especially",
      "dishes",
      "package",
      "from"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Papier",
    "correct": "paper",
    "choices": [
      "foreign country",
      "female tourist",
      "river",
      "paper"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Papiere",
    "correct": "papers, documents",
    "choices": [
      "stairway",
      "Clock",
      "papers, documents",
      "Request / Appeal / You're welcome"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Parfüm",
    "correct": "perfume",
    "choices": [
      "thunderstorm",
      "pot",
      "perfume",
      "tooth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Park",
    "correct": "park",
    "choices": [
      "shoe",
      "park",
      "off / away",
      "in front"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nur",
    "correct": "only / simply",
    "choices": [
      "pen",
      "interesting",
      "to be present / to be there",
      "only / simply"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Partner",
    "correct": "male partner",
    "choices": [
      "newspaper",
      "male partner",
      "talk",
      "thanks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Partnerin",
    "correct": "female partner",
    "choices": [
      "female partner",
      "definitely",
      "different",
      "connection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Party",
    "correct": "party",
    "choices": [
      "party",
      "equal / whatever",
      "repair",
      "Request / Appeal / You're welcome"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Pass",
    "correct": "passport",
    "choices": [
      "pool",
      "passport",
      "celebration",
      "registration"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Obst",
    "correct": "fruit",
    "choices": [
      "theatre",
      "present",
      "fridge",
      "fruit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "oder",
    "correct": "or",
    "choices": [
      "thunderstorm",
      "orange",
      "means of transport",
      "or"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Passwort",
    "correct": "password",
    "choices": [
      "next",
      "bottle",
      "password",
      "why"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Projekt",
    "correct": "project",
    "choices": [
      "bill",
      "project",
      "total",
      "known"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Pause",
    "correct": "pause",
    "choices": [
      "credit",
      "pause",
      "Jeans",
      "sign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Prospekt",
    "correct": "brochure",
    "choices": [
      "known",
      "ending / the end",
      "brochure",
      "note"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Person",
    "correct": "person",
    "choices": [
      "hobby",
      "to do",
      "railway station",
      "person"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Pferd",
    "correct": "horse",
    "choices": [
      "culture",
      "female partner",
      "horse",
      "ice cream"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Pflanze",
    "correct": "plant",
    "choices": [
      "plant",
      "first",
      "therefore / that's why",
      "there"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Prüfung",
    "correct": "exam",
    "choices": [
      "shoe",
      "exam",
      "quality",
      "foreign country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Pullover",
    "correct": "pullover",
    "choices": [
      "pullover",
      "stress",
      "cool",
      "new"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Pizza",
    "correct": "pizza",
    "choices": [
      "healthy",
      "pizza",
      "mobile",
      "tent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Plakat",
    "correct": "poster",
    "choices": [
      "poster",
      "map / city map",
      "sun",
      "proximity / closeness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Plan",
    "correct": "plan",
    "choices": [
      "plan",
      "Long",
      "coffee",
      "accident"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Platz",
    "correct": "place",
    "choices": [
      "tired",
      "afterwards / after that / thereon",
      "person",
      "place"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Qualität",
    "correct": "quality",
    "choices": [
      "quality",
      "leisure",
      "towel",
      "means of transport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Quiz",
    "correct": "quiz",
    "choices": [
      "beautiful",
      "taxi",
      "lots",
      "quiz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Polizei",
    "correct": "police",
    "choices": [
      "police",
      "comic",
      "suit",
      "balcony"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Pommes frites",
    "correct": "French fries",
    "choices": [
      "French fries",
      "time / mark",
      "lock / castle",
      "post code"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Radio",
    "correct": "radio",
    "choices": [
      "company",
      "radio",
      "hall",
      "expensive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Portion",
    "correct": "portion",
    "choices": [
      "out",
      "unfortunately",
      "event",
      "portion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Post",
    "correct": "post",
    "choices": [
      "pause",
      "post",
      "application / canditature",
      "account"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Poster",
    "correct": "poster",
    "choices": [
      "poster",
      "out",
      "offer",
      "forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rathaus",
    "correct": "town hall",
    "choices": [
      "opposite",
      "pause",
      "wish",
      "town hall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Postkarte",
    "correct": "postcard",
    "choices": [
      "ticket",
      "be against",
      "ring",
      "postcard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Postleitzahl",
    "correct": "post code",
    "choices": [
      "female colleague / co-worker",
      "still",
      "spoon",
      "post code"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rätsel",
    "correct": "mystery",
    "choices": [
      "display",
      "mystery",
      "pullover",
      "tent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Praktikum",
    "correct": "internship",
    "choices": [
      "internship",
      "as",
      "without",
      "date"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Raum",
    "correct": "room",
    "choices": [
      "information desk",
      "soccer",
      "center",
      "room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Praxis",
    "correct": "practice",
    "choices": [
      "thunderstorm",
      "practice",
      "unfortunately",
      "celebration"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rechnung",
    "correct": "bill",
    "choices": [
      "bill",
      "out",
      "difference",
      "portion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Preis",
    "correct": "price",
    "choices": [
      "perfume",
      "price",
      "team",
      "file"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "preiswert",
    "correct": "inexpensive",
    "choices": [
      "inexpensive",
      "garage",
      "angry",
      "slowly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "privat",
    "correct": "private",
    "choices": [
      "butter",
      "police",
      "private",
      "who"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "rechts",
    "correct": "right",
    "choices": [
      "free",
      "travel",
      "password",
      "right"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "pro",
    "correct": "per",
    "choices": [
      "all over",
      "per",
      "weak",
      "department store"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "reich",
    "correct": "rich",
    "choices": [
      "scooter",
      "the End",
      "application / canditature",
      "rich"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Problem",
    "correct": "problem",
    "choices": [
      "problem",
      "location",
      "poor",
      "thriller"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Produkt",
    "correct": "product",
    "choices": [
      "cosmetics",
      "landlady",
      "product",
      "face"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Reihe",
    "correct": "line / row / queue",
    "choices": [
      "line / row / queue",
      "fair",
      "union / club",
      "E-Book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Programm",
    "correct": "program",
    "choices": [
      "program",
      "especially",
      "cool",
      "snow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Reinigung",
    "correct": "cleaning",
    "choices": [
      "cafeteria",
      "plan",
      "cleaning",
      "at least"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "rund",
    "correct": "round",
    "choices": [
      "landlord",
      "office",
      "round",
      "to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Reis",
    "correct": "rice",
    "choices": [
      "joke",
      "eye",
      "rice",
      "different"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Reise",
    "correct": "travel",
    "choices": [
      "ending / the end",
      "travel",
      "Disco",
      "map / city map"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Reisebüro",
    "correct": "travel agency",
    "choices": [
      "program",
      "travel agency",
      "Stamp",
      "Attention!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Reiseführer",
    "correct": "travel guide",
    "choices": [
      "ground floor",
      "taxi",
      "travel guide",
      "device"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rundgang",
    "correct": "round tour / circut",
    "choices": [
      "translation",
      "round tour / circut",
      "ship",
      "male pensioner"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sache",
    "correct": "thing",
    "choices": [
      "subject / topic",
      "lemon",
      "error",
      "thing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Saft",
    "correct": "juice",
    "choices": [
      "to be closed",
      "time / mark",
      "slowly",
      "juice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rentner",
    "correct": "male pensioner",
    "choices": [
      "Long",
      "glasses",
      "school",
      "male pensioner"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rentnerin",
    "correct": "female pensioner",
    "choices": [
      "female pensioner",
      "in front",
      "sheet",
      "husband"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Salat",
    "correct": "salad",
    "choices": [
      "salad",
      "female partner",
      "Departure",
      "first"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Salz",
    "correct": "salt",
    "choices": [
      "happiness",
      "heater",
      "salt",
      "fruit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Reparatur",
    "correct": "repair",
    "choices": [
      "repair",
      "definitely",
      "some",
      "noodle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Satz",
    "correct": "sentence",
    "choices": [
      "chain",
      "sentence",
      "room",
      "Bye-bye! / Cheers!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sauber",
    "correct": "clean",
    "choices": [
      "sausage",
      "unemployed",
      "except",
      "clean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sauer",
    "correct": "angry",
    "choices": [
      "sea",
      "garage",
      "angry",
      "bed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rest",
    "correct": "rest",
    "choices": [
      "mystery",
      "so",
      "rest",
      "light"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schade",
    "correct": "a pity",
    "choices": [
      "to be forbidden / to be prohibited",
      "medium",
      "potato",
      "a pity"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Restaurant",
    "correct": "restaurant",
    "choices": [
      "female colleague / co-worker",
      "elevator",
      "restaurant",
      "aim / target"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rezept",
    "correct": "recipe",
    "choices": [
      "last",
      "light",
      "recipe",
      "female customer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schalter",
    "correct": "switch",
    "choices": [
      "be off",
      "switch",
      "everything",
      "road"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rezeption",
    "correct": "reception",
    "choices": [
      "reception",
      "accident",
      "some",
      "umbrella"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "scharf",
    "correct": "sharp",
    "choices": [
      "to be allowed",
      "to do",
      "path",
      "sharp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rind",
    "correct": "beef",
    "choices": [
      "all over",
      "beef",
      "some",
      "cloths / outfit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ring",
    "correct": "ring",
    "choices": [
      "ring",
      "over / past",
      "star",
      "shoe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rock",
    "correct": "skirt",
    "choices": [
      "great",
      "skirt",
      "Bank (Money Institution)",
      "when"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schere",
    "correct": "scissors",
    "choices": [
      "flu",
      "mouth",
      "scissors",
      "timetable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rose",
    "correct": "rose",
    "choices": [
      "sugar",
      "circus",
      "light",
      "rose"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schiff",
    "correct": "ship",
    "choices": [
      "suggestion",
      "suitcase",
      "ship",
      "in / into"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rucksack",
    "correct": "backpack",
    "choices": [
      "urgent",
      "per",
      "backpack",
      "engine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schild",
    "correct": "sign",
    "choices": [
      "for",
      "opposite",
      "sign",
      "homepage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ruhe",
    "correct": "rest",
    "choices": [
      "Apple",
      "mostly",
      "rest",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schirm",
    "correct": "umbrella",
    "choices": [
      "dish",
      "dress",
      "thence / from there",
      "umbrella"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schlafzimmer",
    "correct": "bedroom",
    "choices": [
      "furniture",
      "bedroom",
      "fan",
      "question"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schüler",
    "correct": "male student / pupil",
    "choices": [
      "male student / pupil",
      "file",
      "center",
      "mystery"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schülerin",
    "correct": "female student / pupil",
    "choices": [
      "location",
      "female student / pupil",
      "practice",
      "nature"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schlecht",
    "correct": "bad / poor",
    "choices": [
      "bad / poor",
      "Beginning",
      "in front",
      "date"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schwach",
    "correct": "weak",
    "choices": [
      "breakfast",
      "weak",
      "internet",
      "Colour"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schwanger",
    "correct": "pregnant",
    "choices": [
      "automobile",
      "at least",
      "to be fit",
      "pregnant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schwein",
    "correct": "pig",
    "choices": [
      "problem",
      "to be valid",
      "pig",
      "definitely"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schwer",
    "correct": "heavy",
    "choices": [
      "heavy",
      "ship",
      "but",
      "lady"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schlimm",
    "correct": "bad / worst / upsetting",
    "choices": [
      "corner",
      "bad / worst / upsetting",
      "to there",
      "a lot of"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schloss",
    "correct": "lock / castle",
    "choices": [
      "birthday",
      "amount",
      "lock / castle",
      "ground floor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schwimmbad",
    "correct": "pool",
    "choices": [
      "star",
      "cream",
      "walk",
      "pool"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schluss",
    "correct": "ending / the end",
    "choices": [
      "ending / the end",
      "aim / target",
      "note",
      "landlady"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "See (Teich)",
    "correct": "lake (pond)",
    "choices": [
      "comfortable",
      "soon",
      "stop",
      "lake (pond)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schlüssel",
    "correct": "key",
    "choices": [
      "furniture",
      "thunderstorm",
      "key",
      "letter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "See (Meer)",
    "correct": "sea",
    "choices": [
      "sea",
      "visit",
      "restaurant",
      "group"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schmerz",
    "correct": "pain",
    "choices": [
      "quality",
      "stupid",
      "means of transport",
      "pain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schnee",
    "correct": "snow",
    "choices": [
      "no way",
      "lemon",
      "snow",
      "means of transport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sehenswürdigkeit",
    "correct": "point of interest",
    "choices": [
      "train",
      "price",
      "point of interest",
      "Stamp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Seife",
    "correct": "soap",
    "choices": [
      "soap",
      "number",
      "good",
      "to hurt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sein",
    "correct": "to be",
    "choices": [
      "fun",
      "to be",
      "taxi",
      "which one"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schnell",
    "correct": "fast",
    "choices": [
      "ear",
      "situation",
      "application / canditature",
      "fast"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schokolade",
    "correct": "chocolate",
    "choices": [
      "stairway",
      "chocolate",
      "note",
      "umbrella"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schon",
    "correct": "already / yet",
    "choices": [
      "male pensioner",
      "scholarship",
      "already / yet",
      "pool"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schön",
    "correct": "beautiful",
    "choices": [
      "traffic",
      "beautiful",
      "each",
      "museum"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schrank",
    "correct": "cupboard / closet",
    "choices": [
      "shoe",
      "great",
      "cupboard / closet",
      "restaurant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "an sein",
    "correct": "to be on",
    "choices": [
      "Departure",
      "elevator",
      "male pensioner",
      "to be on"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "aus sein",
    "correct": "be off",
    "choices": [
      "be off",
      "to be closed",
      "exhibition",
      "full"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "auf sein",
    "correct": "to be up",
    "choices": [
      "beer",
      "password",
      "as",
      "to be up"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "weg sein",
    "correct": "to be away",
    "choices": [
      "straight",
      "old",
      "to be away",
      "desire / delight / lust"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zu sein",
    "correct": "to be closed",
    "choices": [
      "to be closed",
      "stupid",
      "center",
      "grade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "seit",
    "correct": "since",
    "choices": [
      "once",
      "radio",
      "wish",
      "since"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Seite",
    "correct": "page",
    "choices": [
      "except",
      "round",
      "page",
      "sometimes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "selbst",
    "correct": "in person / even",
    "choices": [
      "colorful",
      "in person / even",
      "expensive",
      "not correct / wrong"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sendung",
    "correct": "program / show / broadcast",
    "choices": [
      "answer",
      "mineral water",
      "each",
      "program / show / broadcast"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schuh",
    "correct": "shoe",
    "choices": [
      "shoe",
      "people",
      "foreign country",
      "someone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Service",
    "correct": "service",
    "choices": [
      "youth hostel",
      "to be valid",
      "thence / from there",
      "service"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Schule",
    "correct": "school",
    "choices": [
      "female pensioner",
      "park",
      "school",
      "E-Book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sicher",
    "correct": "for sure",
    "choices": [
      "nobody",
      "present",
      "nothing",
      "for sure"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sport",
    "correct": "sport",
    "choices": [
      "trip",
      "beautiful",
      "city",
      "sport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Situation",
    "correct": "situation",
    "choices": [
      "Highway",
      "clean",
      "situation",
      "some"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sportplatz",
    "correct": "sports ground",
    "choices": [
      "on-line",
      "soft",
      "sports ground",
      "item"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sprache",
    "correct": "language",
    "choices": [
      "registration",
      "ski",
      "lock / castle",
      "language"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ski",
    "correct": "ski",
    "choices": [
      "hobby",
      "garage",
      "ski",
      "some"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "so",
    "correct": "so / as",
    "choices": [
      "camera",
      "bridge",
      "male partner",
      "so / as"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sprechstunde",
    "correct": "consultation hour",
    "choices": [
      "Attention!",
      "consultation hour",
      "here",
      "to be up"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Stadt",
    "correct": "city",
    "choices": [
      "Sir",
      "machine",
      "circus",
      "city"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sofa",
    "correct": "sofa",
    "choices": [
      "as",
      "Jeans",
      "sofa",
      "single room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Stadtplan",
    "correct": "map / city map",
    "choices": [
      "later",
      "bag",
      "timetable",
      "map / city map"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Star",
    "correct": "star",
    "choices": [
      "Departure",
      "star",
      "restaurant",
      "shopping mall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sofort",
    "correct": "immediately",
    "choices": [
      "tablet",
      "time / mark",
      "immediately",
      "center"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "stark",
    "correct": "strong",
    "choices": [
      "money",
      "account",
      "male customer",
      "strong"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sogar",
    "correct": "even",
    "choices": [
      "earlier",
      "even",
      "to be on the move / to be out",
      "at least"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sonne",
    "correct": "sun",
    "choices": [
      "camera",
      "to there",
      "cheese",
      "sun"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Stelle",
    "correct": "location",
    "choices": [
      "location",
      "empty",
      "you",
      "so / as"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sonst",
    "correct": "otherwise",
    "choices": [
      "pizza",
      "otherwise",
      "out / afield",
      "stove / cooker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "spannend",
    "correct": "exciting",
    "choices": [
      "exciting",
      "repair",
      "center",
      "aim / target"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Spaß",
    "correct": "fun",
    "choices": [
      "thriller",
      "fun",
      "household",
      "stove / cooker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Stiefel",
    "correct": "boots",
    "choices": [
      "bottle",
      "boots",
      "right",
      "light"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Stift",
    "correct": "pen",
    "choices": [
      "pen",
      "stupid",
      "female student",
      "image"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Stipendium",
    "correct": "scholarship",
    "choices": [
      "sea",
      "scholarship",
      "rest",
      "pregnant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "spät",
    "correct": "late",
    "choices": [
      "taxi",
      "first",
      "sign",
      "late"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "später",
    "correct": "later",
    "choices": [
      "later",
      "Youth (male)",
      "radio",
      "for example"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Stock",
    "correct": "floor",
    "choices": [
      "suitcase",
      "sentence",
      "lock / castle",
      "floor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Stockwerk",
    "correct": "level / floor",
    "choices": [
      "level / floor",
      "to",
      "website",
      "sports ground"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Spaziergang",
    "correct": "walk",
    "choices": [
      "baby",
      "interesting",
      "otherwise",
      "walk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Strand",
    "correct": "beach",
    "choices": [
      "link",
      "beach",
      "team",
      "class"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Straße",
    "correct": "road",
    "choices": [
      "rest",
      "total",
      "road",
      "easy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Straßenbahn",
    "correct": "tram",
    "choices": [
      "belly",
      "international",
      "tram",
      "without"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Speisekarte",
    "correct": "menu",
    "choices": [
      "Jeans",
      "skirt",
      "afterwards / after that / thereon",
      "menu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Spiel",
    "correct": "game",
    "choices": [
      "supermarket",
      "image",
      "game",
      "normal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "streng",
    "correct": "strict",
    "choices": [
      "strict",
      "male customer",
      "pregnant",
      "noodle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Stress",
    "correct": "stress",
    "choices": [
      "once",
      "stress",
      "foods / groceries",
      "still"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Stück",
    "correct": "piece",
    "choices": [
      "piece",
      "elevator",
      "Colour",
      "boots"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Telefon",
    "correct": "phone",
    "choices": [
      "practice",
      "town hall",
      "backpack",
      "phone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Student",
    "correct": "male student",
    "choices": [
      "line / row / queue",
      "male student",
      "Boy",
      "equal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Studentin",
    "correct": "female student",
    "choices": [
      "over / past",
      "contract",
      "female student",
      "person"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Teller",
    "correct": "plate",
    "choices": [
      "hobby",
      "bakery",
      "under",
      "plate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tennis",
    "correct": "tennis",
    "choices": [
      "Jeans",
      "tennis",
      "size",
      "suitcase"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Studium",
    "correct": "studies / academic studies",
    "choices": [
      "thick",
      "late",
      "studies / academic studies",
      "Mrs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Stuhl",
    "correct": "chair",
    "choices": [
      "to be on the move / to be out",
      "permission",
      "tomato",
      "chair"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Termin",
    "correct": "meeting",
    "choices": [
      "meeting",
      "back",
      "bus",
      "portion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "teuer",
    "correct": "expensive",
    "choices": [
      "reception",
      "rice",
      "song",
      "expensive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Text",
    "correct": "text",
    "choices": [
      "male student / pupil",
      "text",
      "travel guide",
      "salt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Theater",
    "correct": "theatre",
    "choices": [
      "theatre",
      "out",
      "at least",
      "heater"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "super",
    "correct": "great",
    "choices": [
      "great",
      "key",
      "sheet",
      "forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Thema",
    "correct": "subject / topic",
    "choices": [
      "subject / topic",
      "dark",
      "angry",
      "heater"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ticket",
    "correct": "ticket",
    "choices": [
      "ticket",
      "TV",
      "display",
      "workshop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Supermarkt",
    "correct": "supermarket",
    "choices": [
      "supermarket",
      "neck",
      "otherwise",
      "contact"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Suppe",
    "correct": "soup",
    "choices": [
      "soup",
      "ground floor",
      "TV",
      "lake (pond)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "tief",
    "correct": "deep",
    "choices": [
      "male student",
      "city",
      "deep",
      "machine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tier",
    "correct": "animal",
    "choices": [
      "out",
      "animal",
      "road",
      "to be forbidden / to be prohibited"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "süß",
    "correct": "sweet",
    "choices": [
      "Jeans",
      "sweet",
      "whiteboard",
      "sports ground"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tipp",
    "correct": "tip",
    "choices": [
      "you",
      "flu",
      "taxi",
      "tip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Titel",
    "correct": "title",
    "choices": [
      "information desk",
      "title",
      "application / canditature",
      "sport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Toilette",
    "correct": "toilet",
    "choices": [
      "toilet",
      "definitely",
      "dead",
      "you"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "toll",
    "correct": "great",
    "choices": [
      "alone",
      "great",
      "female tourist",
      "excuse / apology"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tomate",
    "correct": "tomato",
    "choices": [
      "traffic",
      "fun",
      "nearly",
      "tomato"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Topf",
    "correct": "pot",
    "choices": [
      "to",
      "pot",
      "continue",
      "different"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tablet",
    "correct": "tablet",
    "choices": [
      "small",
      "tablet",
      "cheese",
      "immediately"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tablette",
    "correct": "pill / tablet",
    "choices": [
      "tooth",
      "pill / tablet",
      "to be forbidden / to be prohibited",
      "pain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Torte",
    "correct": "cake",
    "choices": [
      "cake",
      "idea",
      "sharp",
      "young"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "tot",
    "correct": "dead",
    "choices": [
      "island",
      "all over",
      "dead",
      "Request / Appeal / You're welcome"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tafel",
    "correct": "whiteboard",
    "choices": [
      "hotel",
      "whiteboard",
      "strong",
      "offer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "total",
    "correct": "total",
    "choices": [
      "total",
      "some",
      "talk",
      "forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tour",
    "correct": "trip",
    "choices": [
      "bakery",
      "year of birth",
      "product",
      "trip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tasche",
    "correct": "bag",
    "choices": [
      "bag",
      "intelligent",
      "cheese",
      "cat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tourist",
    "correct": "male tourist",
    "choices": [
      "male tourist",
      "beer",
      "what",
      "desire / delight / lust"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Touristin",
    "correct": "female tourist",
    "choices": [
      "cafeteria",
      "greeting",
      "female tourist",
      "interview"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Taschengeld",
    "correct": "pocket money",
    "choices": [
      "butter",
      "kitchen",
      "pocket money",
      "postcard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tasse",
    "correct": "cup",
    "choices": [
      "thunderstorm",
      "cup",
      "rice",
      "nowhere"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Taxi",
    "correct": "taxi",
    "choices": [
      "scooter",
      "still / however / but",
      "taxi",
      "mobile phone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Training",
    "correct": "training",
    "choices": [
      "chocolate",
      "automobile",
      "to have an appointment",
      "training"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Traum",
    "correct": "dream",
    "choices": [
      "feels sorry for (so.) / feels sorry about (sth.)",
      "dream",
      "account",
      "(to go) there"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Team",
    "correct": "team",
    "choices": [
      "driver's license",
      "whiteboard",
      "team",
      "tip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tee",
    "correct": "tea",
    "choices": [
      "earlier",
      "tea",
      "wine",
      "popular"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "unbedingt",
    "correct": "absolutely",
    "choices": [
      "absolutely",
      "cool",
      "cleaning",
      "movie theater"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "und",
    "correct": "and",
    "choices": [
      "and",
      "male colleague / co-worker",
      "shopping mall",
      "a pity"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Treppe",
    "correct": "stairway",
    "choices": [
      "stairway",
      "animal",
      "sweet",
      "visit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Unfall",
    "correct": "accident",
    "choices": [
      "female friend / female acquaintance",
      "except",
      "accident",
      "to be allowed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Universität",
    "correct": "university",
    "choices": [
      "university",
      "interesting",
      "big",
      "slowly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "unter",
    "correct": "under",
    "choices": [
      "hair",
      "intelligent",
      "under",
      "ground floor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "tschüs",
    "correct": "Bye-bye! / Cheers!",
    "choices": [
      "both",
      "orange",
      "hunger",
      "Bye-bye! / Cheers!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "T-Shirt",
    "correct": "T-Shirt",
    "choices": [
      "just",
      "T-Shirt",
      "Luggage",
      "in"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "tun",
    "correct": "to do",
    "choices": [
      "out",
      "company",
      "to do",
      "club"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tür",
    "correct": "door",
    "choices": [
      "door",
      "town hall",
      "computer",
      "line / row / queue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Unterkunft",
    "correct": "accommodation",
    "choices": [
      "quiet",
      "volleyball",
      "engine",
      "accommodation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Unterricht",
    "correct": "class",
    "choices": [
      "pub / tavern / restaurant",
      "Building site / construction site",
      "toilet",
      "class"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Unterschied",
    "correct": "difference",
    "choices": [
      "garage",
      "difference",
      "sometimes",
      "glad"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "über",
    "correct": "above / about",
    "choices": [
      "furniture",
      "above / about",
      "male friend / male acquaintance",
      "ticket"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "überall",
    "correct": "all over",
    "choices": [
      "feels sorry for (so.) / feels sorry about (sth.)",
      "all over",
      "city",
      "means of transport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Unterschrift",
    "correct": "signature",
    "choices": [
      "by",
      "signature",
      "mouth",
      "place of birth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "unterwegs sein",
    "correct": "to be on the move / to be out",
    "choices": [
      "blog",
      "to be on the move / to be out",
      "male boss",
      "first"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Urlaub",
    "correct": "vacation",
    "choices": [
      "shopping mall",
      "project",
      "lock / castle",
      "vacation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Übersetzung",
    "correct": "translation",
    "choices": [
      "male student",
      "class",
      "translation",
      "for sure"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "verabredet sein",
    "correct": "to have an appointment",
    "choices": [
      "ear",
      "potato",
      "cat",
      "to have an appointment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Uhr",
    "correct": "Clock",
    "choices": [
      "forward",
      "accident",
      "because",
      "Clock"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "um",
    "correct": "around",
    "choices": [
      "around",
      "cat",
      "stress",
      "place"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Veranstaltung",
    "correct": "event",
    "choices": [
      "blouse",
      "event",
      "receiver",
      "arm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "verboten sein",
    "correct": "to be forbidden / to be prohibited",
    "choices": [
      "especially",
      "credit",
      "to be forbidden / to be prohibited",
      "full"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Verein",
    "correct": "union / club",
    "choices": [
      "credit",
      "union / club",
      "E-Book",
      "at"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Umzug",
    "correct": "move",
    "choices": [
      "male student / pupil",
      "comic",
      "move",
      "ear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Volleyball",
    "correct": "volleyball",
    "choices": [
      "in / into",
      "lamp",
      "volleyball",
      "so"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "von",
    "correct": "from",
    "choices": [
      "registration",
      "fat",
      "from",
      "person"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vor",
    "correct": "in front",
    "choices": [
      "scooter",
      "dress",
      "in front",
      "link"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vorbei",
    "correct": "over / past",
    "choices": [
      "ice cream",
      "over / past",
      "illness",
      "dream"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Verkehr",
    "correct": "traffic",
    "choices": [
      "traffic",
      "skirt",
      "year of birth",
      "bicycle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Verkehrsmittel",
    "correct": "means of transport",
    "choices": [
      "female tourist",
      "Bank (seating)",
      "snow",
      "means of transport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vorher",
    "correct": "before",
    "choices": [
      "before",
      "move",
      "scissors",
      "nothing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vorne",
    "correct": "ahead / in front",
    "choices": [
      "in / into",
      "after",
      "ahead / in front",
      "Bean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Vorname",
    "correct": "first given name",
    "choices": [
      "Call",
      "first given name",
      "delay",
      "snow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Vorschlag",
    "correct": "suggestion",
    "choices": [
      "suggestion",
      "letter / character",
      "mailbox",
      "male pensioner"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Vermieter",
    "correct": "landlord",
    "choices": [
      "landlord",
      "flight",
      "hard",
      "excuse / apology"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Vermieterin",
    "correct": "landlady",
    "choices": [
      "shoe",
      "landlady",
      "Fashion",
      "shirt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vorwärts",
    "correct": "forward",
    "choices": [
      "tablet",
      "forward",
      "adult",
      "cake"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wach",
    "correct": "awake",
    "choices": [
      "awake",
      "pill / tablet",
      "basketball",
      "ground floor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Verspätung",
    "correct": "delay",
    "choices": [
      "tree",
      "French fries",
      "internship",
      "delay"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wahr",
    "correct": "TRUE",
    "choices": [
      "TRUE",
      "union / club",
      "basketball",
      "for"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wald",
    "correct": "forest",
    "choices": [
      "flower",
      "in person / even",
      "all / quite",
      "forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Vertrag",
    "correct": "contract",
    "choices": [
      "present",
      "tram",
      "glad",
      "contract"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "viel",
    "correct": "a lot of",
    "choices": [
      "a lot of",
      "quiz",
      "sick",
      "spouse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "viele",
    "correct": "lots",
    "choices": [
      "last",
      "neck",
      "lots",
      "cash register"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wann",
    "correct": "when",
    "choices": [
      "pharmacy",
      "book",
      "enough",
      "when"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "warm",
    "correct": "warm",
    "choices": [
      "cap",
      "warm",
      "TV",
      "especially"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Vogel",
    "correct": "bird",
    "choices": [
      "job",
      "sea",
      "but",
      "bird"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "voll",
    "correct": "full",
    "choices": [
      "child",
      "story",
      "exhibition",
      "full"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "warum",
    "correct": "why",
    "choices": [
      "camera",
      "opposite",
      "light",
      "why"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "was",
    "correct": "what",
    "choices": [
      "post",
      "what",
      "right",
      "juice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wenn",
    "correct": "when / if",
    "choices": [
      "ground floor",
      "lemon",
      "when / if",
      "tip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wer",
    "correct": "who",
    "choices": [
      "more",
      "round",
      "who",
      "time / mark"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wem",
    "correct": "to whom / to who",
    "choices": [
      "earlier",
      "soft",
      "to whom / to who",
      "too / also"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wäsche",
    "correct": "cloths / laundry",
    "choices": [
      "dish",
      "cool",
      "cloths / laundry",
      "ground floor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wasser",
    "correct": "water",
    "choices": [
      "water",
      "private",
      "male boss",
      "face"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Werkstatt",
    "correct": "workshop",
    "choices": [
      "face",
      "workshop",
      "address",
      "there"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wettbewerb",
    "correct": "competition",
    "choices": [
      "outside",
      "competition",
      "mobile phone",
      "discount"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wetter",
    "correct": "weather",
    "choices": [
      "thin",
      "cake",
      "first given name",
      "weather"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Webseite",
    "correct": "website",
    "choices": [
      "Highway",
      "experience",
      "holiday",
      "website"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wie",
    "correct": "as",
    "choices": [
      "lamp",
      "as",
      "male pensioner",
      "connection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wie viel",
    "correct": "how much",
    "choices": [
      "how much",
      "mouth",
      "male partner",
      "person"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "weg",
    "correct": "off / away",
    "choices": [
      "off / away",
      "switch",
      "education",
      "guitar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wieder",
    "correct": "again",
    "choices": [
      "again",
      "E-Book",
      "(to go) there",
      "Thank you"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Weg",
    "correct": "path",
    "choices": [
      "living room",
      "path",
      "service",
      "umbrella"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wehtun",
    "correct": "to hurt",
    "choices": [
      "meeting",
      "timetable",
      "to hurt",
      "fat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wind",
    "correct": "wind",
    "choices": [
      "out",
      "outside",
      "wind",
      "game"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "weich",
    "correct": "soft",
    "choices": [
      "lemon",
      "soft",
      "out / afield",
      "pregnant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "weil",
    "correct": "because",
    "choices": [
      "traffic light",
      "because",
      "language",
      "colorful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wein",
    "correct": "wine",
    "choices": [
      "pencil",
      "bus",
      "wine",
      "walk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "weit",
    "correct": "far",
    "choices": [
      "suggestion",
      "far",
      "to have a cold",
      "Apple"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "weiter",
    "correct": "continue",
    "choices": [
      "thick",
      "receiver",
      "continue",
      "tip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "welcher",
    "correct": "which one",
    "choices": [
      "door",
      "mostly",
      "which one",
      "excuse / apology"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Witz",
    "correct": "joke",
    "choices": [
      "joke",
      "mystery",
      "basketball",
      "place"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wo",
    "correct": "where",
    "choices": [
      "on-line",
      "cream",
      "more",
      "where"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "woher",
    "correct": "from where",
    "choices": [
      "absolutely",
      "flea market",
      "female customer",
      "from where"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wohin",
    "correct": "where to",
    "choices": [
      "where to",
      "out / afield",
      "word",
      "fruit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Welt",
    "correct": "world",
    "choices": [
      "pig",
      "world",
      "drug",
      "man"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wenigstens",
    "correct": "at least",
    "choices": [
      "Long",
      "no way",
      "at least",
      "paper"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wohnung",
    "correct": "flat / appartment",
    "choices": [
      "meeting",
      "flat / appartment",
      "thence / from there",
      "animal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wohnzimmer",
    "correct": "living room",
    "choices": [
      "living room",
      "exhibition",
      "rest",
      "suit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wolke",
    "correct": "cloud",
    "choices": [
      "cloud",
      "weak",
      "scissors",
      "T-Shirt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zimmer",
    "correct": "room",
    "choices": [
      "inexpensive",
      "thin",
      "suit",
      "room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zirkus",
    "correct": "circus",
    "choices": [
      "landlady",
      "tooth",
      "circus",
      "movie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Workshop",
    "correct": "seminar / workshop",
    "choices": [
      "tooth",
      "seminar / workshop",
      "just",
      "exam"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zitrone",
    "correct": "lemon",
    "choices": [
      "tablet",
      "far",
      "a few",
      "lemon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zoo",
    "correct": "zoo",
    "choices": [
      "wine",
      "breakfast",
      "name",
      "zoo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zu",
    "correct": "to",
    "choices": [
      "to",
      "portion",
      "normal",
      "printer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wort",
    "correct": "word",
    "choices": [
      "radio",
      "horse",
      "immediately",
      "word"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wunsch",
    "correct": "wish",
    "choices": [
      "ring",
      "otherwise",
      "wish",
      "idea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zucker",
    "correct": "sugar",
    "choices": [
      "on-line",
      "Jeans",
      "for example",
      "sugar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zuerst",
    "correct": "first",
    "choices": [
      "thriller",
      "and",
      "first",
      "to be forbidden / to be prohibited"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wurst",
    "correct": "sausage",
    "choices": [
      "sausage",
      "before",
      "opinion",
      "recipe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zug",
    "correct": "train",
    "choices": [
      "train",
      "small",
      "husband",
      "Answering machine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zuletzt",
    "correct": "last",
    "choices": [
      "when / if",
      "last",
      "intelligent",
      "head"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zahl",
    "correct": "number",
    "choices": [
      "number",
      "and",
      "game",
      "place"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zahn",
    "correct": "tooth",
    "choices": [
      "tree",
      "tooth",
      "school",
      "male tourist"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zum Beispiel",
    "correct": "for example",
    "choices": [
      "from",
      "cash register",
      "country",
      "for example"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zurück",
    "correct": "back",
    "choices": [
      "back",
      "male student / pupil",
      "cupboard / closet",
      "over / past"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zeit",
    "correct": "time",
    "choices": [
      "male tourist",
      "chocolate",
      "time",
      "means of transport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zeitschrift",
    "correct": "magazine",
    "choices": [
      "link",
      "magazine",
      "directly",
      "female customer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zeitung",
    "correct": "newspaper",
    "choices": [
      "phone",
      "back then",
      "newspaper",
      "to be on"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zelt",
    "correct": "tent",
    "choices": [
      "department store",
      "address",
      "full",
      "tent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zentrum",
    "correct": "center",
    "choices": [
      "bread",
      "size",
      "tired",
      "center"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zettel",
    "correct": "note",
    "choices": [
      "note",
      "church",
      "brochure",
      "pain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Zeugnis",
    "correct": "certificate / school report",
    "choices": [
      "plant",
      "certificate / school report",
      "back then",
      "(music) band"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ziel",
    "correct": "aim / target",
    "choices": [
      "female partner",
      "Colour",
      "movie theater",
      "aim / target"
    ]
  }
];